capitalcube.com 2013-01-17

# CapitalCube » Fundamental Analysis, Corporate Actions and Earnings Quality for over 40000 Global Equities

### PRIVACY POLICY

 **Effective: July 27 th 2012**

Welcome to AnalytixInsight Inc. (“AnalytixInsight”) owner of  [www.capitalcube.com](http://www.capitalcube.com/) (the “Site”). Protecting your privacy is important to us. We collect and keep as little information as possible about you.

AnalytixInsight wants you to know what information we learn about you when you visit the Site, what we do with that information, and what choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used.

In no event shall you be entitled to any compensation for the use of any of your personal information.

This Privacy Policy applies to any information we collect on the Site, in e-mail or any other electronic messages between you and AnalytixInsight, and through mobile or desktop applications you download from this Site or any app store or third party provider, which allow for dedicated and non-browser based interactions between you and AnalytixInsight. Any information we collect offline, or any information collected by any third party accessible from or through the Site is not covered by this Privacy Policy.

AnalytixInsight Inc. has been awarded TRUSTe’s Privacy Seal signifying that this privacy policy and practices have been reviewed by TRUSTe for compliance with [TRUSTe’s program requirements](http://www.truste.com/privacy_seals_and_services/consumer_privacy/privacy-programs-requirements.html) including transparency, accountability and choice regarding the collection and use of your personal information.  The TRUSTe program does not cover information that may be collected through downloadable software.   TRUSTe’s mission, as an independent third party, is to accelerate online trust among consumers and organizations globally through its leading privacy trustmark and innovative trust solutions. If you have questions or complaints regarding our privacy policy or practices, please contact us at notices@AnalytixInsight.com.  If you are not satisfied with our response you can contact [TRUSTe here](http://watchdog.truste.com/pvr.php?page=complaint)

 **Security.**  When you send confidential personal account data or sensitive data (such as credit card number) to us on our Site, we require that a “secure session” first be established using Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology. SSL is a security protocol for commercial transactions on the Internet. SSL uses public-key cryptography to authenticate Internet servers, to encrypt data, and to maintain the accuracy of transmitted data.

The security of your personal information is important to us.  We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission an once we receive it.  No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however.  Therefore, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

 **Information Collection.**  When you visit our Site, we recognize only your apparent network address (IP address). Apart from when you register for an account with us, the only way we will see your personal information, such as your name, address, phone number or e-mail address, is if you provide it to us by filling out a form or sending us an e-mail message . We use the information that you provide to us when you register on a page on this Site, fill out a survey, or otherwise voluntarily tell us about yourself or your activities for our own use to improve our products and services and the content of this site. You may also receive mailings or other communications from AnalytixInsight. We currently do not and intend to not sell or pass on any of your information to third parties. We always offer you the option to decline any or all of these communications by clicking the unsubscribe link in our e-mails or by sending an e-mail message to us at [notices@AnalytixInsight](mailto:notices@AnalytixInsight).com  telling us that you do not want to receive e-mail or other mail from AnalytixInsight.

Our Site does, however, use “cookies” to collect information about how our site is used. See “ABOUT COOKIES” below. Information, such as the server your computer is logged onto, your browser type (e.g., Internet Explorer or Firefox), and whether you responded to a banner ad on our Site or e-mail, as well as any stored preferences of our registered users that may be stored in “cookies,” is collected and tracked in aggregate. This information is used for purposes of measuring response rates to banner ads and e-mail offers, as well as for measuring and improving our Site and for providing Site analytics that may be useful for us to sell or develop our products, services or advertising to third parties.

 **Registration for Online Products and Services.**  In order to provide you with a particular product or service online, we may request that you voluntarily supply us with personal information, including your e-mail address and credit card information, for purposes such as correspondence, Site registration, checking your account status online, making a purchase or participating in online surveys, and enabling us to provide an online product or service to you in an efficient manner. If you are known to us as a registered AnalytixInsight online customer, we may combine information about your use of our Site and the online product or service you utilize with certain other online and offline information we have about you as an AnalytixInsight customer and information you have provided to us as well as information available from external sources, such as census bureau data, in order to customize your online experience and present you with relevant online and offline offers and updates.

We also use a “cookie” to enable our server to recognize you as a registered AnalytixInsight online customer when you re-enter our Site, your email and password will be saved. You may turn off our cookies either in your browser settings or in your account settings without impeding the site’s functionality. If you turn off cookies entirely, the site will not recognize you as a registered AnalytixInsight online customer, and you may have to re-enter certain information.

 **Information Use.**  We may use information you have given us to, for example, provide a service, allow you to screen and research stocks, set up alerts, allow you to create or import portfolios, ensure proper billing, measure consumer interest in our various services and inform you about products and services. If you have provided your e-mail address to us or to a company we have partnered with to make their products and services available to you, we may send you e-mail offers. We may also send you e-mail offers if you have provided your e-mail address to a third party and have actively chosen or requested, on an opt-in basis, to receive e-mail offers from other parties. These offers may be based on information you provided in your initial transaction with us, in surveys, from information that may indicate purchasing preferences and lifestyle, as well as information available from external sources, such as census bureau data. These e-mail offers come directly from AnalytixInsight. You can always opt out from receiving e-mail offers from AnalytixInsight as described below in the section, “DECLINING E-MAIL OFFERS.”

When we send e-mails to you, we may be able to identify information about your e-mail address, such as whether you can read graphic-rich html e-mails. If your e-mail address is html-enabled, we may choose to send you graphic-rich html e-mails.

Please note that we do not provide your e-mail address to our business partners. However, we may send you offers on behalf of our business partners. Keep in mind that if you take advantage of an offer from an AnalytixInsight business partner and become their customer, they may independently wish to send offers to you. In this case, you will need to inform them separately if you wish to decline receiving future offers from them.

Our goal is to deliver offers to people who we believe will find them of value. Offers are developed and managed under strict conditions designed to safeguard the security and privacy of customer personal information.

 **Declining E-mail, Direct Mail or Telemarketing Offers.**  AnalytixInsight provides customers with an easy means to decline receiving e-mail, direct mail or telemarketing offers. Although some customers tell us they appreciate receiving notice of these carefully designed opportunities, we recognize the importance of providing you with choices. At any time, you may request to discontinue receiving these offers from us by changing your preferences in your account, or by following the link provided in any promotional email we send you or by emailing us at notices@AnalytixInsight.com. All e-mail, direct mail or telemarketing offers that you receive from AnalytixInsight will inform you of how to decline receiving further such offers.

 **Facebook Connect or other OpenID provider** **.  **You can log in to our site using sign-in services such as Facebook Connect or an Open ID provider. These services will authenticate your identity and provide you the option to share certain personal information with us such as your name and email address to pre-populate our sign up form.  Services like Facebook Connect give you the option to post information about your activities on this Web site to your profile page to share with others within your network.    ****

 **Commitment to Privacy.**  This Privacy Statement applies only to our United States customers and U.S. visitors to our Site. If you are a U.S. customer and have questions about our online Privacy Statement or your account, please send us e-mail at [notices@AnalytixInsight.com.](mailto:notices@AnalytixInsight.com.)  You may also request a copy of the Privacy Statement we posted prior to the updates made to this document. AnalytixInsight Sites in non-U.S. markets have developed Internet privacy statements that are fully consistent with this Customer Privacy Statement. These may be modified as needed for particular products and services, or to conform to local laws or customs around the world.

 **We provide links to third party sites.**  We try to alert you wherever possible when you will be leaving our site, but we may not be able to do so all of the time. As we do not control these web sites, we encourage you to review the privacy policies posted on these and all third party sites. You should be aware that other Internet sites which you access from our Site might contain privacy provisions that differ from the provisions of our Privacy Statement.

 **About Cookies.**  Cookies were originally designed to help a web site distinguish a user’s browser as a previous visitor and thus save and remember any preferences that may have been set while the user was browsing the Site. A cookie is a small string of text that a web site can send to your browser. A cookie cannot retrieve any other data from your hard drive, pass on computer viruses, or capture your e-mail address. Currently, web sites use cookies to enhance the user’s visit; in general, cookies can securely store a user’s email address and password, personalize home pages, identify which parts of a site have been visited or keep track of selections.

If you are just browsing our Site, a cookie identifies only your browser. If you become a registered online customer of AnalytixInsight (with a designated email address and password), we use cookies so that we can provide customized information that we believe will be of value to you based on preferences indicated, other information we have about you as an AnalytixInsight customer, as well as information available from external sources such as the census bureau. The preferences in your cookies are available to us for reviewing and measuring the analytics of how our Site is being used, and such data is aggregated by us. It is possible to set your browser to inform you when a cookie is being placed. This way, you have the opportunity to decide whether to accept the cookie. If you are just browsing our Site and are not a registered online customer, you do not have to accept a cookie and you may continue visiting the Site.

The use of cookies by third parties is not covered by our privacy policy.  We do not have access or control over these cookies.

 **Third Party Sharing**

We will share your personal information with third parties only in ways that are described in this privacy policy.  We do not sell your personal information to third parties.

–      We may provide your personal information to companies that provide services to help us with our business activities such as sending out emails on our behalf or offering customer service. These companies are authorized to use your personal information  _only as necessary to provide  _these services to us.  The support section of our site is hosted by our third party service provider, in order to submit a support request you must first create an account and provide your name and email address.  You also may upload a photo once you have created an account, participate in forums, or check on existing requests.  Please note that all information collected within these forms is governed by our service providers privacy policy.

–      We may also disclose your personal information

–      as required by law, such as to comply with a subpoena, or similar legal process

–      when we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, or respond to a government request,

–      if we are involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of our assets,  you will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our Web site of any change in ownership or uses of your personal information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal information.

 **Public Forums**

Our Web site offers publicly accessible blogs or community forums. You should be aware that any information you provide in these areas may be read, collected, and used by others who access them. To request removal of your personal information from our blog or community forum, contact us at notices@AnalytixInsight.com.  In some cases, we may not be able to remove your personal information, in which case we will let you know if we are unable to do so and why.

 **Social Media (Features) and Widgets**

Our Web site includes Social Media Features, such as the Facebook Like button and Widgets, such as the Share this button or interactive mini-programs that run on our site. These Features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our site, and may set a cookie to enable the Feature to function properly. Social Media Features and Widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our Site. Your interactions with these Features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it.

 **Customer Testimonials**

We post customer testimonials on our web site which may contain personally identifiable information.  We do obtain the customer’s consent via email prior to posting the testimonial to post their name along with their testimonial.

 **Access to Personally Identifiable Information**

If your personally identifiable information changes, or if you no longer desire our service, you may correct, delete inaccuracies, or update it by making the change on our member information page or by emailing our Customer Support at [notices@AnalytixInsight.com](mailto:notices@AnalytixInsight.com). We will respond to your request to access within 30 days.

 **Data Retention**

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. If you wish to cancel your account or request that we no longer use your information to provide you services contact us at notices@AnalytixInsight.com.  We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

 **Changes in this Privacy Policy**

We may update this privacy policy to reflect changes to our information practices. If we make any material changes we will notify you by email (sent to the e-mail address specified in your account) or by means of a notice on this Site prior to the change becoming effective. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices.

 **Contact Us**

If you have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us at:

notices@AnalytixInsight.com

AnalytixInsight Inc.

1123 Broadway

Suite 613

New York, NY 10010
